Finding Aid for the George Alexander Heard Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
George Alexander Heard Papers
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0201
577.50 linear_feet
- Correspondence (Outgoing & Incoming) (Ab-Be)
  - - Abernathy, Minna K. (Box 1)
  - - Abram, Irwin (Box 1)
  - - Abse, D.W. (Box 1)
  - Acheson "Declaration" (Box 1)
  - Adams, Deborah Douglas (Box 1)
  - Abercrombie, Billy Joe (Box 1)
  - Aberle, Sophie Bledsoe (Box 1)
  - Adams, E.M. (Box 1)
  - Adams, Francis L. (Box 1)
  - Adams, J. Stacy (Box 1)
  - Adams, Marguerite M. (Box 1)
  - Adams, Raymond (Box 1)
  - Address File (Manilla Envelope) (Box 1)
  - Adkins, Dorothy C. (Box 1)
  - Aerojet: General Corporation (Box 1)
  - Adder, Robert E. (Box 1)
  - Ahlander, Bjorn (Box 1)
  - Aircraft Owners & Pilot's Association (Box 1)
  - Ahlswede, Gretchen (Box 1)
  - Alabama, University of Press (Box 1)
  - Albright, R. Mayne (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Frank (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Herbert E. (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Will Winton (Box 1)
  - Allen, Byron G. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Ethan P. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Mildred (Mrs. Ward P. Allen) (Box 1)
  - Allen, Walter Jr. (Box 1)
  - Allcott, John (Box 1)
  - Allied Van Lines Claim (Box 1)
  - Almond, Gabriel (Box 1)
  - Alumni Annual Giving (Box 1)
  - American Academy of Political Science (Box 1)
  - American Associataion for United Nations (Box 1)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 1)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 1)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 1)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 1)
  - America for Democratic Action (Box 1)
  - American Indian Fund (Box 1)
  - American Men of Science (Box 1)
  - American Political Science Association (Box 1)
  - American Society for Public Admin. (Box 1)
  - American Veteran Commission (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Don (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Donald B. (Box 1)
  - Andrews, George C. (Box 1)
  - Andrus, Helen S. (Box 1)
  - Appleby, Paul H. (Box 1)
  - Applewhite, Marjorie M. (Box 1)
  - Apter, David (Box 1)
  - Armstrong, Roy (Box 1)
  - Arnall, Ellie (Box 1)
  - Arrarte, Maria S. (Box 1)
  - Ashby, Dick (Box 1)
  - Ashby, Warren (Box 1)
  - Ashmore, Harry S. (Box 1)
  - Atkinson, George S. (Box 1)
  - Atlantic Union Committee (Box 1)
  - Ayres, Douglas W. (Box 1)
  - Atlanta Urban League (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous A's (Box 1)
  - Bacher, Edward L. (Box 1)
  - Baer, Herbert R.. (Box 1)
  - Bahnson, Agnew G., Jr. (Box 1)
  - Bailely, James H. Pou (Box 1)
  - Bailey, J.O. (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Stephen K. (Box 1)
  - Baity, H.G. (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Stephen K. (Box 1)
  - Balch, Richard H (Box 1)
  - Baldwin, Roger (Box 1)
  - Balfour, Nancy (Box 1)
  - Ballerstedt, Louise (Mrs. G.H.Raggio) (Box 1)
  - Barbaro, J.R.Commander (Box 1)
  - Barghorn, Frederick (Box 1)
  - Barker, Florence A (Box 1)
  - Barnes, F.J. II (Box 1)
  - Barnet, Redmond (Box 1)
  - Barnett, Joseph Yooh (Box 1)
  - Bartley, Ernest R (Box 1)
  - Barton, Kenneth H (Box 1)
  - Battle, Ben (Box 1)
  - Battle, Laurie C (Box 1)
  - Battles, James (Box 1)
  - Bauer, Raymond A (Box 1)
  - Baum, Werner A (Box 1)
  - Beach, Leonard B (Box 1)
  - Beach, Waldo (Box 1)
  - Beale, Howard K (Box 1)
  - Beam, M.P (Box 1)
  - Beardslee, Walter E (Box 1)
  - Beaton, Harold (Box 1)
  - Beer, Samuel H (Box 1)
  - Beers, Frederic L (Box 1)
  - Bell, Mack (Box 1)
  - Bell, Malcolm Jr (Box 1)
  - Benson Aircraft Corporation (Box 1)
  - Berelson, Bernard (Box 1)
- Correspondence (Outgoing & Incoming) (Be-Co)
  - Berg, Randy (Box 2)
  - Berle, Adolf A. Jr (Box 2)
  - Bernd, Joseph L (Box 2)
  - Bernstein, Samuel (Box 2)
  - Beshara, John J (Box 2)
  - Bethel, Millard (Box 2)
  - Biggers, George C (Box 2)
  - Bills, Subscriptions, Etc (Box 2)
  - Biltmore Hotel: The College Department (Box 2)
  - Bingham, Barry (Box 2)
  - Binz, E.O (Box 2)
  - Birsall, Benjamin (Box 2)
  - Birdsall, Donald (Box 2)
  - Birdsau, Donald (Box 2)
  - Black, Anna (Box 2)
  - Black, Bedford W (Box 2)
  - Black, E. Miss (Box 2)
  - Black, Robert S. Jr (Box 2)
  - Blackwell, Gordon W (Box 2)
  - Blaine, James G (Box 2)
  - Blair, William McC. Jr (Box 2)
  - Bland, Earney (Box 2)
  - Bligh, Walter E (Box 2)
  - Bloomfield, Charles A (Box 2)
  - Bodfish, Jeanne S (Box 2)
  - Boggs, Hale (Box 2)
  - Boke, Richard (Box 2)
  - Bond, Niles W (Box 2)
  - Bond, Professor Richmond P (Box 2)
  - Bone, Hugh A (Box 2)
  - Bonnet, Ellis A (Box 2)
  - Book-of-the-Month Club (Box 2)
  - Bookwalter, W.F (Box 2)
  - Borgstrom, Aug (Box 2)
  - Bothwell, Eva Hope (Box 2)
  - Boughton, Winona (Box 2)
  - Boyd, Bernard (Box 2)
  - Brandis, Henry Jr (Box 2)
  - Bradley, Phillips (Box 2)
  - Bradshaw, Francis F (Box 2)
  - Brashear, J.C (Box 2)
  - Brecht, E.A (Box 2)
  - Breen, Margaret (Box 2)
  - Brickell, Herschel (Box 2)
  - Bridge, Franklin (Box 2)
  - Bridgforth, Walter (Box 2)
  - British Information Service (Box 2)
  - Broadhurst, Austin (Box 2)
  - Brookings Institute (Box 2)
  - Brooks Brothers Clothing (Box 2)
  - Brown, Dyke (Box 2)
  - Brown, William D (Box 2)
  - Browne, Duff (Box 2)
  - Bryant, Victor S (Box 2)
  - Bryars, William D (Box 2)
  - Buchanan, William (Box 2)
  - Budlong, Connie Sue (Box 2)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists (Box 2)
  - Bullitt, James B (Box 2)
  - Bunting, Fred (Box 2)
  - Burdette, Franklin L (Box 2)
  - Bureau of the Census (Box 2)
  - Bureau of the Public Administration (Box 2)
  - Brug, Frank E (Box 2)
  - Burgess, David S. (Georgia State Industrial Union Council) (Box 2)
  - Burgess, Mary (Box 2)
  - Burres, Jim (Box 2)
  - Bush, George R (Box 2)
  - Busk, Carolyn (Box 2)
  - Butler, David (Box 2)
  - Butler, Edward A (Box 2)
  - Byck, Mildred (Box 2)
  - Byrn, Jim (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous B's (Box 2)
  - Cacioppa, Anne B (Box 2)
  - Cadek, Ottokar (Box 2)
  - Cadden-Allen Advertising Agency (Box 2)
  - Cadmus, Robert (Box 2)
  - Cahan, Avery (Box 2)
  - Cain, Harry P (Box 2)
  - Caldwell, John Tyler (Box 2)
  - Caldwell, William S (Box 2)
  - Calhoun, Alan (Box 2)
  - Calhoun, Julian: Claims Service (Box 2)
  - Calkins, Robert D (Box 2)
  - Callcott, Robert D (Box 2)
  - Cameron, Ed (Box 2)
  - Campbell, Alan K (Box 2)
  - Campbell, Angus (Box 2)
  - Cannington, Grace Miss (Box 2)
  - Cannon, Emily C (Box 2)
  - Carleton, William G (Box 2)
  - Carmichael, James V (Box 2)
  - Carmichael, Katherine (Box 2)
  - Carmichael, Oliver C (Box 2)
  - Carolina Inn (Box 2)
  - Carolina Politcal Union (Box 2)
  - Carpenter, Ray (Box 2)
  - Carroll, D.D (Box 2)
  - Carroll, Thomas H (Box 2)
  - Carter, Hodding Mr (Box 2)
  - Carter, Roy E. Jr (Box 2)
  - Cartier, R.W (Box 2)
  - Carver, Joan (Box 2)
  - Carver, Laurence N (Box 2)
  - Case, Clifford P (Box 2)
  - Cater, Douglass (Box 2)
  - Catlin, George (Box 2)
  - Chambers, Lenoir (Box 2)
  - Chambers, William N (Box 2)
  - Chapel of the Cross Restoration Fund (Box 2)
  - Chapin, Stuart (Box 2)
  - Chapman, Oscar L (Box 2)
  - Clark, Henry (Box 2)
  - Clark, Richard N (Box 2)
  - Charlesworth, James C (Box 2)
  - Chase, John L (Box 2)
  - Childs, Richard S (Box 2)
  - Chubb, Lyle R (Box 2)
  - CIRCULATION: Kansas City Star, The Chronicle, The Milwaukee Journal, The Eugene Register-Guard (Box 2)
  - Citizens Committee on D.P.'s (Displaced Persons) (Box 2)
  - Civil Service Commission (Box 2)
  - Clark, Alice (Box 2)
  - Clark, Richard N. Jr (Box 2)
  - Clayton, John S (Box 2)
  - Cleaveland, Frederic N (Box 2)
  - Cleaveland, Marilyn (Box 2)
  - Cleaveland, Gordon B (Box 2)
  - Clevenger, Clinton B (Box 2)
  - The Club (Box 2)
  - Coates, Albert (Box 2)
  - Cobb, Daisy S (Box 2)
  - Cockburn, S. Herbert (Box 2)
  - Cochrane, William M (Box 2)
  - Coffey, Gene Mrs (Box 2)
  - Coffey, Greta H (Box 2)
  - Coker, Francis W (Box 2)
  - Cole, Gordon H (Box 2)
  - Cole, Taylor (Box 2)
  - Colegrove, Kenneth (Box 2)
  - Coleman, Ann (Box 2)
  - Collier, Charles Allen (Box 2)
  - Collier, Charles W (Box 2)
  - Collier, John (Box 2)
- Correspondence (Outgoing & Incoming) (Co-El)
  - Collins, LeRoy (Box 3)
  - Coltrain, Joan Carol (Box 3)
  - Columbia University (Box 3)
  - Comer, Donald (Box 3)
  - Committee for Alabama (Box 3)
  - Committee ont eh Chancellor (Box 3)
  - Committee for the Marshall Plan to Aid European Society (Box 3)
  - Community Council (Old Discarded Notes) Chapel Hill (Box 3)
  - Comption, Arthur (Box 3)
  - Connelly, John W. Jr., Mrs (Box 3)
  - Connery, Robert H (Box 3)
  - Cook, Olan Victor (Box 3)
  - Cook, Peggy (Box 3)
  - Cook, Thomas I (Box 3)
  - Comer, Harry F (Box 3)
  - "Committee of 100" (Box 3)
  - Coombs, Philip H (Box 3)
  - Cooper, Bertram (Box 3)
  - Cooper, Peter P (Box 3)
  - Cooper, Weldon (Box 3)
  - Cooperative Broadcasting Association Incorporated (Box 3)
  - Cope, Ansley (Box 3)
  - Corbett, Paul D (Box 3)
  - Corry, John A (Box 3)
  - Cosmos Club (Box 3)
  - Cottell, Phillip (Box 3)
  - Cotten, Lyman (Box 3)
  - Coulson, C.A (Box 3)
  - Coultier, E. Merton (Box 3)
  - Council Against Intolerance in America (Box 3)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc (Box 3)
  - Craig, Newton (Box 3)
  - Craige, Archibald (Box 3)
  - Craige, Ernest (Box 3)
  - Craigeill, Frank (Box 3)
  - Cram, George F (Box 3)
  - Crawford, W.B. Jr (Box 3)
  - Crisp, Lucy Cherry (Box 3)
  - Crittenden, John (Box 3)
  - Cruciani, Frances (Box 3)
  - Culbertson, John Bolt (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, Gwendolyn (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, James V. Jr (Box 3)
  - Cunningham, John R. Jr (Box 3)
  - Curlin, Claud (Box 3)
  - Curtis, Billie Miss (Box 3)
  - Curtis, Carl T (Box 3)
  - Curtis, Ernest (Box 3)
  - "C" Miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Dabney, Virginius (Box 3)
  - Daley, Richard J (Box 3)
  - Daniels, Frank A (Box 3)
  - Daniels, Jonathan (Box 3)
  - Dannenbaum, M.N (Box 3)
  - Darden, Colgate W. Jr (Box 3)
  - Dardenne, P.D (Box 3)
  - Darrow, R.M (Box 3)
  - Dasher, Gordon Wayne (Box 3)
  - Dashiell, F.K (Box 3)
  - Dauer, Manning J (Box 3)
  - David, Paul T (Box 3)
  - David, Paul T (Box 3)
  - Davidson, Al (Box 3)
  - Davidson, Mercedes (Box 3)
  - Davis, Carroll (Box 3)
  - Davis, Junius A (Box 3)
  - Davis, Lambert (Box 3)
  - Dawson, Donald S (Box 3)
  - Dawson, Ray (Box 3)
  - Day, Martha (Box 3)
  - Dean, Alfred (Box 3)
  - DeGrove, John M (Box 3)
  - Delaney, Pat (Box 3)
  - DeMarco, Ronald R (Box 3)
  - Demerath, Nicholas J (Box 3)
  - Demere, R.M (Box 3)
  - Democratice National Committee (Box 3)
  - Denny, George V., Jr (Box 3)
  - Dent, A.W (Box 3)
  - Detroit Area Study (Box 3)
  - DeVinney, Leland (Box 3)
  - Dexter, Lewis, A (Box 3)
  - Dialectic Society (Box 3)
  - Diamont, Alfred (Box 3)
  - Disber, Ken (Box 3)
  - Dishman, Robert B (Box 3)
  - Dixon, William Thomas (Box 3)
  - Doar, Harriet (Box 3)
  - Dobbs, Malcom Cotton (Box 3)
  - Dolan, Joseph F (Box 3)
  - Donald, W.J (Box 3)
  - Dooley, Arch R (Box 3)
  - Dorsey, John T (Box 3)
  - D'Orsay, Richard Franklin (Box 3)
  - Doty, Dale E (Box 3)
  - Douglas, Louis H (Box 3)
  - Douglas, Paul (Box 3)
  - Douglas, Scotty Miss (Box 3)
  - Dozier, Donald M (Box 3)
  - Drachkovitch Milorad, M (Box 3)
  - Drew, Gerald A (Box 3)
  - Driscoll, Ketherine Morrell (Box 3)
  - Dudley, Tilford E (Box 3)
  - Duenow, Gordon E (Box 3)
  - Duffy, James H (Box 3)
  - Dunlap, Minnie (Box 3)
  - Durden, Robert (Box 3)
  - Durham, Carl T (Box 3)
  - Durham Furniture Company (Box 3)
  - Durham, G. Homer (Box 3)
  - Durisch, L.L (Box 3)
  - "D" - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - D's (Bureau of Public Administration) University of Alabama (Box 3)
  - Easley, Owen, R., Jr (Box 3)
  - Eastern Air Lines (Box 3)
  - Easton, David (Box 3)
  - Ecuador Miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Edison Voicewriter (Box 3)
  - Edsall, Preston W (Box 3)
  - Edson, Peter (Box 3)
  - Edwards, Kate F (Box 3)
  - Ehle, John (Box 3)
  - Elder, J.P (Box 3)
- Correspondence (El-Go)
  - Eldersveld, Samuel J (Box 4)
  - Elkin, Norman (Box 4)
  - Ellegood, Donald R (Box 4)
  - Elmendorf, John (Box 4)
  - Elliot, Ruth (Box 4)
  - Elsbree, Hugh L (Box 4)
  - Emergencey Committee of Atomic Scientists (Box 4)
  - Emory University Library (Box 4)
  - Enarson, Harold L (Box 4)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 4)
  - Engle, James Bruce (Box 4)
  - Engler, Robert (Box 4)
  - E's (Bureau of Public Administration) Research Associate (Box 4)
  - Sessions Laws Correspondence (EPS) (Electoral Process Study) (Box 4)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, George Gray: Report on EPS (Box 4)
  - Office Memorandum -- EPS -- Crawley -- (Box 4)
  - Epting, Wallace (Box 4)
  - Bitter, Margaret (EPS) & Crawley, M.H.: Correspondence & Assignments (Box 4)
  - Ervin, Sam J., Jr (Box 4)
  - Estes, Rice (Box 4)
  - Eulau, Heinz (Box 4)
  - Eure, Thad (Box 4)
  - Evans, Bowen (Box 4)
  - Evans, Marjory (Box 4)
  - Everett, Robinson (Box 4)
  - Everglades, Florida (Box 4)
  - Ewing, Cortex A.M (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous E's (Box 4)
  - Fadum, R.E (Box 4)
  - Faison, Georgia H (Box 4)
  - Farau, Alfred (Box 4)
  - Farber, Evan (Box 4)
  - Fargo, A.J (Box 4)
  - Farley, William T (Box 4)
  - Farmer, Hallie (Box 4)
  - Farris, Charles D (Box 4)
  - Fath, Creekmore (Box 4)
  - Fauske, Ingebert (Box 4)
  - Fay, George Morris (Box 4)
  - Federal Communications Commission (Box 4)
  - Federal Public Housing Authority (Box 4)
  - Feidelson, Charles N (Box 4)
  - Feinberg, Abraham (Box 4)
  - Feiss, Carl (Box 4)
  - Fenton, John H (Box 4)
  - Fenwick, Charles G (Box 4)
  - Feraru, Arthur (Box 4)
  - Ferguson, LeRoy C (Box 4)
  - Ferrell, Marvin L., Jr (Box 4)
  - Fesler, James W (Box 4)
  - Finer, Herman (Box 4)
  - Fink, Arthur E (Box 4)
  - Fjelle, Ethel B (Box 4)
  - Flam, Gerald (Box 4)
  - Fleishman, Joel L (Box 4)
  - Fleming, Harold C (Box 4)
  - Flower, Milton E (Box 4)
  - Fonville, Mary E (Box 4)
  - Ford, Gene A (Box 4)
  - Ford, Pamela (Box 4)
  - Fornari, Josephine A (Box 4)
  - Fortenberry, C.N (Box 4)
  - Fortson, Blanton (Honorable) (Box 4)
  - Fortune (Box 4)
  - Fourie, L (Box 4)
  - Foushee, John (Box 4)
  - Frank Brothers (Box 4)
  - Frazer, K.C (Box 4)
  - Frazier, Robert (Box 4)
  - Freeman, Donald (Box 4)
  - Freedman, Ronald (Box 4)
  - Freeman, Douglas Southall (Box 4)
  - Freeman, J. Leiper (Box 4)
  - French Shriner & Urner (Box 4)
  - Frey, Charles W (Box 4)
  - Friday, William (Box 4)
  - Friederich, Werner P (Box 4)
  - Friedman, Joseph B (Box 4)
  - Friends Service Comittee (American) (Box 4)
  - Friday, William C (Box 4)
  - Fuchs, Lawrence H (Box 4)
  - Fulbright Program: Political Scientists (Box 4)
  - Fuller, Ford P (Box 4)
  - Fuller, Helen (Box 4)
  - Funk, Arthur J (Box 4)
  - Fussler, Karl H (Box 4)
  - F's (Bureau of Public Administration) University of Alabama (Box 4)
  - F - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
  - Gallagher, John F (Box 4)
  - Galvin, John P (Box 4)
  - Gammon, Edgar G (Box 4)
  - Gange, John (Box 4)
  - Garceau, Oliver (Box 4)
  - Gardner, O. Max (Box 4)
  - Garrison, Lloyd K (Box 4)
  - Gass, Edmund C (Box 4)
  - Gates, Jay H (Box 4)
  - Gatlin, Douglas S (Box 4)
  - Gatton, T. Harry (Box 4)
  - General Education Board (Box 4)
  - Georgia Information (Bureau of Public Administration Research Associate) (Box 4)
  - General Motors (Box 4)
  - George, Walter F (Box 4)
  - George Washington University (Box 4)
  - Georgia, University of (Box 4)
  - Georgian Veterans For Majority Rule (Box 4)
  - Georgia Workers Education Service (Box 4)
  - Gibson, Frank K (Box 4)
  - Gil, Federico (Box 4)
  - Gillin, John P (Box 4)
  - Gilmore, Voit (Box 4)
  - "Glen Lennox" (Box 4)
  - Glick, David M (Box 4)
  - Globe and Mail (Toronto) (Box 4)
  - Godfrey, James L (Box 4)
  - Goetz, H (Box 4)
  - Golden Fleece (Box 4)
  - Goldman, Ralph (Box 4)
  - Goldrich, Daniel (Box 4)
  - Goldsmith, Arthur (Box 4)
  - Goodall, Merrill Randall (Box 4)
  - Gooding, Frank (Box 4)
  - Goodman, T.W (Box 4)
  - Goodman, William (Box 4)
  - Gordon, Peggy (Box 4)
  - Gore, Albert (Box 4)
  - Gorrell, Juan Leese (Box 4)
  - Gosnell, Cullen (Box 4)
  - Governmental Research Center (Box 4)
  - Gow, J. Steele (Box 4)
  - Grace, Joan (Box 4)
  - Graduate Schools (Box 4)
  - Graham, Frank Porter (Box 4)
  - Graham, Philip (Box 4)
  - Graham, Willard J (Box 4)
  - Graham, William E., Jr (Box 4)
  - Granger, Mary (Box 4)
  - Graves, Louis (Box 4)
  - Gray, Gibson (Box 4)
  - Gray Gordon, Installation, UNC (Box 4)
  - Great Northern Hotel (Box 4)
  - Green, James W (Box 4)
  - Green, Margaret (Box 4)
  - Green, Paul (Box 4)
  - Greenberg, Bunny (Box 4)
  - Greene, Lee S (Box 4)
  - Greensboro Daily News (Box 4)
  - Greenwood, Gertrude C (Box 4)
  - Greenwood, Gertrude C (Box 4)
  - Greenwood, Gertrude C (Box 4)
  - Greenwood, Hugh (Box 4)
  - Grear, I.G (Box 4)
  - Greer, Richard T (Box 4)
  - Greulach, Victor A (Box 4)
  - Grisette, Felix A (Box 4)
  - Grodzins, Morton (Box 4)
  - Gross, Bertram (Box 4)
  - Gruman, Russell M (Box 4)
  - Guthrie, Daniel (Box 4)
  - Gutierrez, Ernest (Box 4)
  - Guysenir, Maurice G (Box 4)
  - Gwynn, J. Minor (Box 4)
  - Gwyn, William (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous G's (Box 4)
  - Hagberg, Eric (Box 4)
  - Haines, Jones & Company (Box 4)
  - Hale, George (Box 4)
  - Halliburton, Julian D (Box 4)
  - Hallowell, John H (Box 4)
  - Ham, George C (Box 4)
  - Hamerick, Irene (Box 4)
  - Hamilton, Guy (Box 4)
  - Hamilton, J.G.de Roulhac (Box 4)
  - Hamilton, Peter G (Box 4)
  - Hammer, Philip G (Box 4)
  - Hammond, Charlotte (Box 4)
  - Hammond, Louise (Box 4)
  - Hanft, Frank (Box 4)
  - Harcourt, Brace & Company, Inc (Box 4)
  - Harding, Edith, F (Box 4)
  - Harding, Julia (Box 4)
  - Harding, Victor Hunt (Box 4)
  - Hardistry, Mildred (Box 4)
  - Harlow, Rex F (Box 4)
  - Harrill, Earnest E (Box 4)
  - Harris, Frederick H (Box 4)
  - Harris, John R (Box 4)
  - Harris, Roy V (Box 4)
  - Harris, T.C (Box 4)
  - Harris Transfer & Warehouse Company (Box 4)
  - Harrison,William B (Box 4)
  - Hartsell, Earl H (Box 4)
  - Harvey, L.G (Box 4)
  - Hatch, Jerry (Box 4)
  - Hatch, Nancy (Box 4)
  - Hay, Donald G (Box 4)
  - Hayes, Pheobe F (Box 4)
  - Haygood, Vandi V (Box 4)
  - Hayman, Donald (Box 4)
  - Haynie, William Sugar (Box 4)
  - Hays, Brooks (Box 4)
  - Heady, Ferrel (Box 4)
  - Heath, Milton S (Box 4)
  - Hecher, Kenneth W (Box 4)
  - Heerman, Walter (Box 4)
  - Heidenheimer, Arnold J (Box 4)
  - A.J. Heidenheimer (Box 4)
  - Helander, Mel (Box 4)
  - Hennings, Thomas C., Jr (Box 4)
  - Hensley, Robert B (Box 4)
  - Hess, Audrey (Box 4)
  - Hess, Stephen (Box 4)
  - Hickman, C. Addison (Box 4)
  - Highsaw, Robert B (Box 4)
  - Hildebrand, Sara (Box 4)
  - Hill, Reuben (Box 4)
  - Hill, Watts, Jr (Box 4)
  - Hinderacker, Ivan (Box 4)
  - Hobart, Edward A (Box 4)
  - Hobbs, Claude E (Box 4)
  - Hodges, Luther (Box 4)
  - Hoffman, Victor (Box 4)
  - Holcombe, Arthur N (Box 4)
  - Holmes, Jim (Box 4)
  - Holton, Mildred (Box 4)
  - Holtzman, Abraham (Box 4)
  - Hoole, W. Stanley (Box 4)
- (Ho-Ky)
  - Horace Williams Philosphical Society (Box 6)
  - Horn, Andrew H (Box 6)
  - Horner, George F (Box 6)
  - Horton, Myles (Box 6)
  - Hotelling, Harold (Box 6)
  - House, R.B (Box 6)
  - Houston, John A (Box 6)
  - Howard, Helen (Box 6)
  - Howard, Vaughn (Box 6)
  - Howard, Virginia Johnson (Box 6)
  - Howard, Winidfred A (Box 6)
  - Howell, John M (Box 6)
  - Hubbell, Margaret B (Box 6)
  - Humphrey, Peg (Box 6)
  - Hunt, Victor M (Box 6)
  - Hunter, Floyd (Box 6)
  - Huntington, Samuel P (Box 6)
  - Hutchins, Nan (Box 6)
  - Hyneman, Charles (Box 6)
  - H's Miscellaneous (Bureau of Public Administration) (Box 6)
  - Ierardi, Gordon S (Box 6)
  - Illisley, Lucretia L (Box 6)
  - Independent Petroleum Association of America (Box 6)
  - Institute of Ethnic Affairs (Box 6)
  - Institute of International Education (Box 6)
  - Institutio Indigenista Interamericano (Box 6)
  - Institute, Governmental Affairs (Box 6)
  - Institute of Labor & Industrial Relations (Box 6)
  - Institute, Tuskegee (Box 6)
  - Insurance (Box 6)
  - Insurance (Box 6)
  - Insurance (Box 6)
  - Insurance Policies (Box 6)
  - International League for the Rights of Man (Box 6)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 6)
  - Irion, Frederick C (Box 6)
  - Iron Curtain Refugee Campaign (Box 6)
  - Isaacs, Charles (Box 6)
  - Ivanoff, Dimitry N (Box 6)
  - Ivey, Alfred (Box 6)
  - Ivey, John E., Jr (Box 6)
  - Ivey, Julia K (Box 6)
  - Ivey, Pete (Box 6)
  - Jackson, Addie May (Box 6)
  - Jackson, Luther P (Box 6)
  - Jackson, William (Box 6)
  - Jaffe, Alice Cohn (Box 6)
  - James, Clark (Box 6)
  - Jamison, Mary Alice (Box 6)
  - Janowitz, Morris (Box 6)
  - Jenkins, W.S (Box 6)
  - Jilli, E.C (Box 6)
  - Jocher, Katherine (Box 6)
  - Johnson, Clair (Box 6)
  - Johnson, Donald B (Box 6)
  - Johnson, Ferne (Box 6)
  - Johnson, Franklyn Arthur (Box 6)
  - Johnson, Grace E (Box 6)
  - Johnson, Walter (Box 6)
  - Johnstone, William C., Jr (Box 6)
  - Joint Committee to Secure a Fair Trial of the Trenton Six (Box 6)
  - Jolles, Paul (Box 6)
  - Jones, Claiborne (Box 6)
  - Jones, John Price (Box 6)
  - Jones, Tom (Box 6)
  - Jones, Victor (Box 6)
  - Joseph, Sylvan L (Box 6)
  - Joslin Study (Box 6)
  - Journal Company, The (Box 6)
  - Joyce, H.E., Jr (Box 6)
  - Kaneko, Masonori (Box 6)
  - Kansas (Box 6)
  - Kattsoff, L.O (Box 6)
  - Keefe, Arthur J (Box 6)
  - Keefer, Dorothy H (Box 6)
  - Kehauver, Estes (Box 6)
  - Keith-Lucas, Alan (Box 6)
  - Kelly, Stanley Jr (Box 6)
  - Kempers, Bert (Box 6)
  - Kendrick, Jack (Box 6)
  - Kendrick, John W (Box 6)
  - Kessel, John W (Box 6)
  - Ketchum, Carlton G (Box 6)
  - Ketchum, David S (Box 6)
  - Keys, Thomas (Box 6)
  - Kiefer, Charles F. Jr (Box 6)
  - Kilgore, Harley M (Box 6)
  - Killion, George (Box 6)
  - Killpatrick, Ann Carson (Box 6)
  - Kimball, Lindsley F (Box 6)
  - King, Arnold K (Box 6)
  - Kirkpatrick, Evron M (Box 6)
  - Klain, Maurice (Box 6)
  - Knebel, Fletcher (Box 6)
  - Knight, Davis (Box 6)
  - Knight, Davis (Box 6)
  - Knopf, Alfred A (Box 6)
  - Kofmehl, Ken (Box 6)
  - Kohler, Charlotte (Box 6)
  - Kohn, Melvin L (Box 6)
  - Kolb, William L (Box 6)
  - Kowalski, Stanislaw (Box 6)
  - Kulske, W.W (Box 6)
  - Kurtz, Morton (Box 6)
  - Kytle, Calvin (Box 6)
- (La-Mi)
  - Lackey, Katharine (Box 7)
  - LaDow, Charles (Box 7)
  - Laity, Verna (Box 7)
  - Lamb, Bernard (Box 7)
  - Lambert, Richard D (Box 7)
  - Lambeth, Robert Bolling (Box 7)
  - Lambeth, Tom W (Box 7)
  - Lambeth, S.S., Jr (Box 7)
  - Landau, Martin (Box 7)
  - Lane, Robert E (Box 7)
  - Lange, Hermann (Box 7)
  - Langer, William (Box 7)
  - Lanier, Edwin S (Box 7)
  - Lanlan, Y (Box 7)
  - Larson, Donald R (Box 7)
  - Lasley, John Wayne (Box 7)
  - Lassiter, John T (Box 7)
  - Lasswell, Harold D (Box 7)
  - Latham, Earl (Box 7)
  - Latham, Leslie Wade (Box 7)
  - Lathrop, Albert H (Box 7)
  - Lattimore, Ralstrom B (Box 7)
  - Lattimore, William (Box 7)
  - Lawrence, Alex A (Box 7)
  - League of Nations Association, Inc (Box 7)
  - Leavitt, Sturgis E (Box 7)
  - Lederle, John W (Box 7)
  - Leiserson, Avery (Box 7)
  - Lepawsky, Albert (Box 7)
  - Lerner, Max (Box 7)
  - Lester, Robert M (Box 7)
  - Levinskas, A.L. (Russian Scholar) (Box 7)
  - Lewis, Henry W (Box 7)
  - Lewis, John D (Box 7)
  - Liberal Party (Box 7)
  - Liberman, S (Box 7)
  - Liberty National Bank & Trust Co (Box 7)
  - Likert, Rensis (Box 7)
  - Lindsay, Franklin A (Box 7)
  - Lippincott, Benjamin E (Box 7)
  - Litchfield, Edward H (Box 7)
  - Little House, The (Box 7)
  - Loescher, Frank S (Box 7)
  - Long, Boaz (Box 7)
  - Long, Gillis W (Box 7)
  - Long, John B (Box 7)
  - Longshore, Herman K (Box 7)
  - Lovecky, Georgene B (Box 7)
  - Lucy, Mary Lou (Box 7)
  - Ludwig, F.G (Box 7)
  - Lundberg, George A (Box 7)
  - Lynchburg Area University Center (Box 7)
  - Lyons, Clifford (Box 7)
  - Lyons, John C (Box 7)
  - Lytle, Frances (Box 7)
  - Luxon, Norval Neil (Box 7)
  - L's Miscellaneous (Office of Public Administration) (Box 7)
  - Mackay, James (Box 7)
  - MacLeod, John Blount (Box 7)
  - MacMillon, Dougald (Box 7)
  - MacPherson, C.B (Box 7)
  - Mademoiselle (Box 7)
  - Madry, Bob (Box 7)
  - Magill, Robert N (Box 7)